So when you think of the word currency, you probably think of a legal tender, right?
Like the form of money in a particular place.
But the etymology of the word currency is from Latin, career, meaning to run, career, to flow.
Well, sometimes the money do flow, but you know what always flows?
Energy, your energy.
And it's electric, boogie, boogie, boogie.
Your energy is what makes the money circulate.
Your energy is what's been manipulated to even make money valuable.
The people who are running the world are really running on your energy.
So what you give attention to, what you worry about, that's what they're banking on.
Literally banking on.
Now, I know I'm in a black turtleneck and I'm talking in a certain cadence.
This sounds like I might be giving you some hotepery.
But what I'm giving you is facts.
And what I want you to really hear is that your energy is valuable.
That's really all I want you to hear out of this.
Your energy is valuable.
And you have to ask yourself, okay, but like, what is the potency of my energy?
Like, I know my energy is pure.
My energy is not thinned and distilled with hateration, with insecurity.
Every day I'm working to filter out that trauma.
And then when you decolonize, you are better able to control your energy in the direction
you want it to go to versus giving it to them to control it in the direction they want it
to go to.
And them are the billionaire families that are aligned with the Vatican, that control
the banking systems of the world, that steal the resources of the earth, including the
energy of the people of earth.
This is not a Democrat-Republican issue.
How black am I going to have to get?
And I don't think it's possible for this establishment to react to a human problem in a human way.
It's impossible.
In terms of self-interest.
You think it's that inhuman?
It is.
It's obviously that inhuman to me.
If you look at its history and what it's doing now.
If that is human, then we're something else.
So I have to assume that they're non-human.